mipworld.net 2010-11-23

# Privacy policy - MIPWorld

Welcome to Reed MIDEM’s website [www.mipworld.com](http://www.mipworld.com/) (hereafter: the “Portal”). 

Since 1994, Reed MIDEM, member of the Reed Exhibitions group, has been offering Internet services and secure Websites (hereinafter called "the Sites") which are user-friendly and respectful of their users' rights. 

We undertake to respect the privacy of users of these Sites and in particular the Portal. We have consequently prepared this Data Protection Notice (hereafter: the "Privacy Policy") to explain the nature of the information gathered on the Portal when you visit them, and the ways in which it may be used. 

**1\. GENERALITY**  
Reed MIDEM respects the privacy of every individual who visits the Portal, and all other Sites owned, operated or maintained directly or indirectly by Reed MIDEM. 

Reed MIDEM hereby informs you on the terms and conditions under which data that we collect from you on the Portal will be used, shared and otherwise treated. This Privacy Policy will also instruct you on how you can verify the accuracy, and control certain uses, of the information you provide to us on the Portal. Reed MIDEM abides by the constraining French and European rules in terms of protection of personal data and privacy. Personal data processing carried out by Reed MIDEM in the framework of the Portal were notified to the French Data Protection Authority, the CNIL ([www.cnil.fr](http://www.cnil.fr/)). 

The Portal is governed by French law. Any use made of it must comply with its terms and will be deemed to have taken place on French territory. Any access to and/or use of the Portal is deemed to express unreserved acceptance of these Privacy Policy. 

For the purpose of the present privacy policy, Reed MIDEM considers its clients (hereinafter “Clients”) to be:   
• Visitors and PSB (Participant without a stand) to exhibitions,   
• Exhibitors at exhibitions and their affiliates,   
• Conference participants,   
• The press,  
• Sales representatives of Reed MIDEM. 

For any additional information, please contact Reed MIDEM’s team by sending an email to [customerhelpservice@reedmidem.com](mailto:customerhelpservice@reedmidem.com). 

**2\. COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL DATA  
2.1 - Information collected**  
Reed MIDEM collects personal data on Clients, in accordance with the French Data Processing, Data Files and Individual Liberties Law dated January 6th, 1978 through, inter alia, paper and electronic forms used for participation to Reed MIDEM events, answers to satisfaction questionnaires and participation to surveys as run from time to time by Reed MIDEM, information supplied in the course of visiting Reed MIDEM websites, including information provided upon request by Reed MIDEM to allow it to answer queries on Reed MIDEM’s products and services. 

Reed MIDEM distinguishes two kinds of personal data supplied by its Clients which are processed as described below. 

**\- Financial Information**  
Information associated with payments, which is obtained during registration procedures (e.g. credit card numbers, names of financial institutions and credit card expiry dates, listed by way of example but not of limitation) is classed as "Financial Information". 

**\- Business Information**  
Business Information includes Clients’ names, addresses, telephone and fax numbers, e-mail addresses and other personal data related to professional activities. The data collected during a Client's visit to the Portal is classed as “Business Information”. 

**2.2 - Use of Business and Financial Information  
\- Financial information  
**Reed MIDEM uses Financial Information exclusively for purposes of processing registration, as well as for accounting and debt collection purposes. 

**\- Business information**  
Reed MIDEM uses Business Information and share it on a need basis with other organizations, partners or contractors of Reed MIDEM, to enable or to facilitate the performance of contracts entered with the Clients for the supply of products and services as well as to inform them on Reed MIDEM’s similar products and services. Reed MIDEM may also have to disclose Business Information to comply with applicable law and/or court injunction, and to compel respect of rights, property and safety of Reed MIDEM or of third parties. 

As part of Portal online services, Clients have access to a database containing Business Information, to allow them to identify the Clients and to communicate with them using their contact details, including their email addresses. 

**2.3 - Use by Client of other Client’s personal data**  
Each client having authorized access to Portal online services commits to make a use of personal data of other Clients in a good faith manner in compliance with the French Data Processing, Data Files and Individual Liberties Law dated January 6th, 1978 and the standards of Netiquette and conduct of business dealings in terms mutually approved by the concerned Clients. It is prohibited to use the Portal online services to collect or store personal data about other Clients. 

Commercial use of Clients’ personal data made available in the course of the Portal on line services and not expressly agreed by the concerned Client is formally prohibited and subject to court action for remedy. 

The Client is fully liable for conforming with applicable rules, more specifically those set forth in the French Data Processing, Data Files and Individual Liberties Law dated January 6th, 1978, regarding the transfer of personal data of Clients to third countries. 

**3 User rights  
3.1 - Rights guaranteed by the French Privacy Law**  
In accordance with the provisions of French law 78-17 dated January 6th, 1978 related to “Information Technology and Civil liberties” (Law No. 78-17 of 6 January 1978 amended by Law No. 2004-801 of 6 August 2004), if you have previously submitted personal data to Reed MIDEM, you have the right to access, rectify or object to the personal data relating to you. 

You may thereby require any information concerning yourself which would be untrue, incomplete, and ambiguous or obsolete, to be modified, completed, clarified, updated or deleted. 

If you wish to exercise that right, please please [contact us](mailto:contact.cnil@reedmidem.com?subject=Reed%20MIDEM%20/%20MIPWORLD%20Privacy%20Policy%20opt%20out&body=Thank%20you%20for%20not%20sending%20future%20commercial%20offers%20for%20products%20and%20services%20through%20use%20of%20my%20email,%20unless%20to%20respond%20to%20an%20express%20request%20on%20my%20part.).  
Please also note that once we receive your request, it may take up to 3 weeks to become effective.

**3.2 - Rights provided by the Trusting Digital Economy Law**  
In accordance with the provisions of the French law 2004-575 dated June 21st, 2004 related to « Trusting Digital Economy”, you have the right to opt out of receiving future marketing communication from Reed MIDEM through use of your electronic contact details. 

If you wish to opt out, please click hereunder:  
[Thank you for not sending future commercial offers for products and services through use of my email, unless to respond to an express request on my part.](mailto:contact.cnil@reedmidem.com?subject=Reed%20MIDEM%20/%20MIPWORLD%20Privacy%20Policy%20opt%20out&body=Thank%20you%20for%20not%20sending%20future%20commercial%20offers%20for%20products%20and%20services%20through%20use%20of%20my%20email,%20unless%20to%20respond%20to%20an%20express%20request%20on%20my%20part.)

**4\. SECURITY**   
The Portal managed by Reed MIDEM uses a secure server to protect financial and business data. To the extent that the Portal offer secure server software, it is used to encrypt the information exchanged between your Web browser and our the Portal. This measure ensures the security of your business and financial transactions when you use the Portal. We follow strict security procedures when filing and using the information you supply, and may request proof of your identity before supplying you with business information. We take all reasonable steps to ensure the secrecy of your personal data and passwords. 

You are fully responsible for maintening the confidentiality of your password and abstaining from communicating it to any other person and you are solely liable for activities that occur under your password and login. Reed MIDEM disclaims all liabilities for inaccuracy of your personal data and in case of theft, loss, misuse, communication, fraudulent use of your login and password arising from your failure to comply with the above. 

**5\. USE OF COOKIES**   
The Portal may use cookies in the case of on-line purchase procedures to ensure the smooth operation of your on-line payments, to facilitate your registration procedures and to eliminate the need to input information that you have already provided during a previous visit to the Portal, or in the case of sections protected by a password. 

Cookies are small information files that a website can send to the hard disk of a personal computer for traceability reasons. They are not executable programs, and cannot contain viruses or applications. The cookies used only take up a minimal amount of space on your hard disk. 

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. However, you can always prevent cookies from being recorded on your computer by using the options provided by your browser.If you do so, some parts of the Portal may not operate as well as they should. 

For more information on cookies and configuration of your web browser, you may visit the French data protection authority website at: <http://www.cnil.fr/index.php?id=42>. 

**6\. LINKS TO OTHER SITES**   
The Portal provides links to third-party websites managed by other companies than Reed MIDEM. Reed MIDEM neither publishes nor monitors the sources and content of these websites nor their links with other sites. 

Due to the open communication nature of the Internet, Reed MIDEM cannot guarantee that communications between you and the Portal, and the Portal and you, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. Users of the Portal use these sites at their own risk. 

The links to these third-party websites that may also collect personal and non personal data, in no manner constitute Reed MIDEM’s approval or validation with the contents of these websites nor Reed MIDEM’s association with the owners and/or the publishers, designers, webmasters, managers or hosts of these websites who each should have their own privacy policy and data collection practices, independent of Reed MIDEM and the Portal. 

Reed MIDEM cannot be held liable for their contents, products, services, advertising, cookies, computer code, or for the use of the data you supply to those websites as well as for any and all money damages or losses, whether proven or alleged, consecutive to or while using the information, services or data available on these sites. Reed MIDEM provides these links for the convenience of the visitors to the Portal and such visitors access these websites at their own risk. 

**7\. STATISTICS**   
The Portal is regularly monitored in order to supply you with the best service and to meet your expectations. For this purpose, we consult the statistics relating to use of the Portal and develop the Portal on the basis of this data. User statistics are anonymous. 

**8\. ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND AMENDMENTS**   
Reed MIDEM reserves the right to modify or, in general, to update this notice at any time to change in the law or for other reasons, which we reserve the right to do without prior notice. 

These modifications will enter into force as soon as they are posted online on the Portal. Therefore you are invited to visit the Portal’s version which is constantly online. If Reed MIDEM changes this Privacy Policy, your continued use of the Portal following the posting of such changes will signify your acceptance of those changes. 

Test 2 Scheduled Publishing by Serge - page published at 1.00 pm
